[
    {
        "question": "In what year was Minecraft fully released?",
        "answerA": 2012,
        "answerB": 2011,
        "answerC": 2007,
        "answerD": 2010,
        "correct": 1
    }, {
        "question": "How many players can play together, at the same time, on Minecraft Realms?", 
        "answerA": 12,
        "answerB": 8,
        "answerC": 11,
        "answerD": 10,
        "correct": 3
    }, {
        "question": "The game follows a day and night cycle. How long does one full cycle last in real-time?",
        "answerA": "20 minutes",
        "answerB": "30 minutes",
        "answerC": "60 minutes",
        "answerD": "10 minutes",
        "correct": 0
    }, {
        "question": "Which of the following cannot be tamed?",
        "answerA": "Wolf",
        "answerB": "Ocelot",
        "answerC": "Chicken",
        "answerD": "Horse",
        "correct": 2
    }, {
        "question": "What item do you need to make all of the potions?",
        "answerA":"Water bottle",
        "answerB": "Gun powder",
        "answerC": "Blaze Powder",
        "answerD": "Nether Wart",
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "Which species began due to a coding error?",
        "answerA": "Slime",
        "answerB": "Piglin",
        "answerC": "Drowned",
        "answerD": "Creeper",
        "correct": 3
    },{
        "question": "What must you use to mine ores and stones?",
        "answerA": "Iron Pickaxe",
        "answerB": "Axe",
        "answerC": "Stone Pickaxe",
        "answerD": "Wooden Pickaxe",
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "To make one iron ingot, how many slabs of iron ore do you need?",
        "answerA": 2,
        "answerB": 0,
        "answerC": 1,
        "answerD": 5,
        "correct": 2
    },{
        "question": "Axolotl can come in how many different colors?",
        "answerA": 5,
        "answerB": 6,
        "answerC": 2,
        "answerD": 7,
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "Which creature has 2 hearts?",
        "answerA": "Chicken",
        "answerB": "Fish",
        "answerC": "Rabbit",
        "answerD": "Pig",
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "How many types of flowers are there? ",
        "answerA": 18,
        "answerB": 13,
        "answerC": 17,
        "answerD": 15,
        "correct": 2
    },{
        "question": "To create 1 iron pickaxe, what materials do you need?",
        "answerA": "2 sticks and 2 iron ingots",
        "answerB": "2 sticks and 1 iron ingots",
        "answerC": "1 sticks and 2 iron ingots",
        "answerD": "3 sticks and 2 iron ingots",
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "The sounds made by Ghasts come from what real animal? ",
        "answerA": "Lion",
        "answerB": "Lynx",
        "answerC": "Cheetah",
        "answerD": "Cat",
        "correct": 3
    },{
        "question": "What language is Enderman?",
        "answerA": "Russian",
        "answerB": "English backwards",
        "answerC": "German",
        "answerD": "French backwards",
        "correct": 1
    },{
        "question": "What was the game initially going to be called?",
        "answerA": "Block Game",
        "answerB": "Mine Game",
        "answerC": "Cave Game",
        "answerD": "Craft Block",
        "correct": 2
    },{
        "question": "What is terrified of Ocelots?",
        "answerA": "Zombie",
        "answerB": "Creepers",
        "answerC": "Skeleton",
        "answerD": "Wolf",
        "correct": 1
    },{
        "question": "What item can sugar cane make?",
        "answerA": "Paper",
        "answerB": "Cookie",
        "answerC": "Book and quill",
        "answerD": "Maps",
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "A Husk is a type of zombie found in only one place. Where is this?",
        "answerA": "Water",
        "answerB": "Village",
        "answerC": "Desert",
        "answerD": "Jungle",
        "correct": 2
    },{
        "question": "What creature can you control with a carrot on a stick?",
        "answerA": "Stryder",
        "answerB": "Rabbit",
        "answerC": "Donkey",
        "answerD": "Pigs",
        "correct": 3
    },{
        "question": "As well as hay bales, what else will a Llama eat?",
        "answerA": "Sugar",
        "answerB": "Wheat",
        "answerC": "Carrots",
        "answerD": "Grass",
        "correct": 1
    },{
        "question": "What problem does tonic cure?", 
        "answerA": "Poison",
        "answerB": "Blindness",
        "answerC": "Nausea",
        "answerD": "Hunger",
        "correct": 2
    },{
        "question": "How many sets of wool must you have to make a bed?",
        "answerA": 3,
        "answerB": 2,
        "answerC": 4,
        "answerD": 1,
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "What color is Steve's outfit?",
        "answerA": "Blue",
        "answerB": "Turquoise",
        "answerC": "Cyan",
        "answerD": "Light Blue",
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "What is the rarest item in Minecraft?",
        "answerA": "Totem of Undying",
        "answerB": "Dragon egg",
        "answerC": "Beacon",
        "answerD": "Music Disc",
        "correct": 1
    },{
        "question": "How many BAFTA awards has the game won?",
        "answerA": 0,
        "answerB": 1,
        "answerC": 2,
        "answerD": 3,
        "correct": 3
    }
    ]
